

# **NADYA PAK**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER 1 YEAR EXPERIENCE

## **Summary:**

Hello.

I am Nadya, 31 years old, Front-End Developer with creative and logical thinking. Love coding and create something new. Open-minded for new technologies for me like **VueJs**, **React**, easy-going and responsible. I would like to join to friendly team with interesting tasks and use my best skills to contribute in something great.

## **Experience:**

2019-2021 ALROSA PJSC (Moscow) Frontend-developer

ALROSA is the leader of the world diamond mining industry. There I was responsible for developing UI of web application based on **Angular 8**.

**2010-2019** ALROSA PJSC (Moscow) Sales support specialist

#### **Education:**

2018-2019

Courses Web-developer "Skillbox" (Moscow), student.

2015-2018

Higher School of Economics, Bachelor's degree, IT business analytics.

2007-2013

Moscow State Mining University (MSMU), Process engineer.

#### **Skills:**

- JavaScript
- Typescript
- Angular
- 00P
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- MySQL
- Git
- Agile and Scrum
- Trello
- Iira
- Azure

### Languages:

- English
- Hebrew
- Russian

## **Tools:**

- Windows & Linux
- Visual Studio Code
- SublimeText

#### **Contacts:**

Location: Bat -Yam, Israel

E-mail: Nadegda.park1707@gmail.com

**Phone:** (+972) 58-553-69-21

**LinkedIn:** <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/park-nadegda">https://www.linkedin.com/in/park-nadegda</a>